<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--
	String Encrypt(string, key[, algorithm[, encoding[, IVorSalt[, iterations]]]]))
-->
<function xmlns="http://www.cfeclipse.org/version1/dictionary"
	name="encrypt" returns="String">
	<help><![CDATA[
		Encrypts a string. Uses a symmetric key-based algorithm, in
		which the same key is used to encrypt and decrypt a string.
		The security of the encrypted string depends on maintaining
		the secrecy of the key. Uses an XOR-based algorithm that uses
		a pseudo-random 32-bit key, based on a seed passed by the user
		as a function parameter.
	]]></help>
	<parameter name="String" type="String" required="true">
		<help><![CDATA[
			String to encrypt.
		]]></help>
	</parameter>
	<parameter name="key" type="String" required="true">
		<help><![CDATA[
			Key or seed used to encrypt the string.
			* For the CFMX_COMPAT algorithm, any combination of any
			  number of characters; used as a seed used to generate
			  a 32-bit encryption key.
			* For all other algorithms, a key in the format used by the
			  algorithm. For these algorithms, use the GenerateSecretKey
			  function to generate the key.
		]]></help>
	</parameter>
	<parameter name="algorithm" type="String" required="false">
		<help><![CDATA[
			The algorithm to use to encrypt the string. 
			* CFMX_COMPAT: the algorithm used in ColdFusion MX and prior
			  releases. This algorithm is the least secure option (default).
			* AES: the Advanced Encryption Standard specified by the
			  National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) FIPS-197.
			* BLOWFISH: the Blowfish algorithm defined by Bruce Schneier.
			* DES: the Data Encryption Standard algorithm defined by NIST FIPS-46-3.
			* DESEDE: the "Triple DES" algorithm defined by NIST FIPS-46-3.
		]]></help>
		<values default="CFMX_COMPAT">
			<value option="CFMX_COMPAT" />
			<value option="AES" />
			<value option="BLOWFISH" />
			<value option="DES" />
			<value option="DESEDE" />
		</values>
	</parameter>
	<parameter name="encoding" type="String" required="false">
		<help><![CDATA[
			The binary encoding used to represent the data as a string.
			Must be the same as the algorithm used to encrypt the string.
			* Base64: the Base64 algorithm, as specified by IETF RFC 2045.
			* Hex: the characters A-F and 0-9 represent the hexadecimal byte values.
			* UU: the UNIX standard UUEncode algorithm (default).
			If you specify this parameter, you must also specify the algorithm parameter.
		]]></help>
		<values default="UU">
			<value option="UU" />
			<value option="Base64" />
			<value option="Hex" />
		</values>
	</parameter>
	<parameter name="ivorsalt" type="Binary" required="false">
		<help><![CDATA[
			Specify this parameter to adjust ColdFusion encryption to match
			the details of other encryption software. If you specify this
			parameter, you must also specify the algorithm parameter.
			* For Block Encryption Algorithms: This is the binary
			  Initialization Vector value to use with the algorithm. The
			  algorithm must contain a Feedback Mode other than ECB. This
			  must be a binary value that is exactly the same size as the
			  algorithm block size.
			* For Password Based Encryption Algorithms: This is the binary
			  Salt value to transform the password into a key.
		]]></help>
	</parameter>
	<parameter name="iterations" type="Numeric" required="false">
		<help><![CDATA[
			The number of iterations to transform the password into a
			binary key. Specify this parameter to adjust ColdFusion
			encryption to match the details of other encryption software.
			If you specify this parameter, you must also specify the
			algorithm parameter with a Password Based Encryption (PBE)
			algorithm. Do not specify this parameter for Block Encryption
			Algorithms. You must use the same value to encrypt and
			decrypt the data.
			* For Password Based Encryption Algorithms: This is the
			  binary Salt value to transform the password into a key.
		]]></help>
	</parameter>
</function>
