<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--
	cfcollection
		action = "action"
		collection = "collection_name"
		path = "path_to_verity_collection"
		language = "language"
		name = "queryname"
		categories = "true" or "false"
-->
<tag xmlns="http://www.cfeclipse.org/version1/dictionary"
	name="cfcollection" single="true" xmlstyle="false">
	<help><![CDATA[
		Creates, registers, and administers Verity search engine
		collections.

		A collection that is created with the cfcollection tag is
		internal. A collection created any other way is external.

		A collection that is registered with CFML using the
		cfcollection tag or registered with the K2 Server by editing
		the k2server.ini file is registered. Other collections are
		unregistered.
	]]></help>
	<return type="cfcollection" parameter="name" />
	<parameter name="action" type="String" required="true">
		<help><![CDATA[
			categorylist: retrieves categories from the collection and
				indicates how many documents are in each one. Returns
				a structure of structures in which the category
				representing each substructure is associated with a
				number of documents. For a category in a category tree,
				the number of documents is the number at or below that
				level in the tree.
			create: registers the collection with CFML.
				- If the collection is present: creates a map to it
				- If the collection is not present: creates it
			delete: unregisters a collection.
				- If the collection was registered with action = create:
					deletes its directories
				- If the collection was registered and mapped: does not
					delete collection directories
			optimize: optimizes the structure and contents of the
				collection for searching; recovers space.
			list: returns a query result set, named from the name
				attribute value, of the attributes of the collections
				that are registered by CFML and K2 Server.
			map: creates a map to the collection. It is not necessary
				to specify this value. Deprecated in CF7.
			repair: fixes data corruption in a collection. Deprecated in CF7.
		]]></help>
		<values default="list">
			<value option="categorylist" />
			<value option="create" />
			<value option="delete" />
			<value option="optimize" />
			<value option="list" />
			<value option="map" compatibility="deprecated" />
			<value option="repair" compatibility="deprecated" />
		</values>
	</parameter>
	<parameter name="collection" type="String" required="false">
		<help><![CDATA[
			A collection name. The name can include spaces
		]]></help>
		<values />
	</parameter>
	<parameter name="path" type="String" required="false">
		<help><![CDATA[
			Absolute path to a Verity collection.
		]]></help>
		<values />
	</parameter>
	<parameter name="language" type="String" required="false">
		<help><![CDATA[
			Options are listed in Usage section. Requires the
			appropriate (European or Asian) Verity Locales language
			pack.
		]]></help>
		<values default="english" />
	</parameter>
	<parameter name="name" type="variableName" required="false">
		<help><![CDATA[
			Name for the query results returned by the list action.
		]]></help>
		<values />
	</parameter>
	<parameter name="categories" type="boolean" required="false">
		<help><![CDATA[
			Used only for creating a collection:
			 - true: This collection includes support for categories.
			 - false: This collection does not support categories. Default.
		]]></help>
		<values default="false">
			<value option="true" />
			<value option="false" />
		</values>
	</parameter>
</tag>
