<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--
	cfcontent
		type = "file_type"
		deleteFile = "boolean"
		file = "filename"
		reset = "boolean"
	[starting with a drive letter and a colon, or a forward
	or backward slash]
-->
<tag xmlns="http://www.cfeclipse.org/version1/dictionary"
	name="cfcontent" single="true" xmlstyle="false">
	<help><![CDATA[
		Does either or both of the following:
		* Sets the MIME content encoding header for the current page
		* Sends the contents of a file from the server as the page
			output
	]]></help>
	<parameter name="type" type="String" required="false">
		<help><![CDATA[
			The MIME content type of the page, optionally followed by
			a semicolon and the character encoding. By default,
			CFML sends pages as text/html content type in
			the UTF-8 character encoding.
		]]></help>
		<values />
	</parameter>
	<parameter name="deletefile" type="boolean" required="false">
		<help><![CDATA[
			Applies only if you specify a file with the file attribute.
			
			Yes: deletes the file on the server after sending its
				contents to the client.
			No: leaves the file on the server.
		]]></help>
		<values default="false">
			<value option="true" />
			<value option="false" />
		</values>
	</parameter>
	<parameter name="file" type="String" required="false">
		<help><![CDATA[
			Name of file whose contents will be the page output. When
			using CFML in a distributed configuration, the file
			attribute must refer to a path on the system on which the
			web server runs. When you use this attribute, any other
			output on the current CFML page is ignored; only the
			contents of the file is sent to the client.
		]]></help>
		<values />
	</parameter>
	<parameter name="variable" type="String" required="false"><!-- VariableName -->
		<help><![CDATA[
			Name of a ColdFusion MX binary variable whose contents can
			be displayed by the browser, such as the contents of a chart
			generated by the cfchart tag or a PDF or Excel file
			retrieved by a cffile action="readBinary" tag.
			When you use this attribute, any other output on the current
			CFML page is ignored; only the contents of the file are sent
			to the client.
		]]></help>
		<values />
	</parameter>
	<parameter name="reset" type="boolean" required="false">
		<help><![CDATA[
			The reset and file attributes are mutually exclusive.
			If you specify a file, this attribute has no effect.

			Yes: discards output that precedes call to cfcontent
			No: preserves output that precedes call to cfcontent. In
			this case all output is sent with the specified type.
		]]></help>
		<values default="true">
			<value option="true" />
			<value option="false" />
		</values>
	</parameter>
</tag>
