<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tag xmlns="http://www.cfeclipse.org/version1/dictionary" creator="3" name="cfquery" single="false" xmlstyle="false">
			<help><![CDATA[
				Passes queries or SQL statements to a data source.
				It is recommended that you use the cfqueryparam tag within
				every cfquery tag, to help secure your databases from
				unauthorized users
			]]></help>
			<parameter name="name" required="false" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Name of query. Used in page to reference query record set.
					Must begin with a letter. Can include letters, numbers,
					and underscores.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="datasource" required="false" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Name of data source from which query gets data.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="dbtype" required="false" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					query. Use this value to specify the results of a query as
					input.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="username" required="false" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Overrides username in data source setup.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="password" required="false" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Overrides password in data source setup.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="maxrows" required="false" type="Numeric">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Maximum number of rows to return in record set.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="blockfactor" required="false" type="Numeric">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Maximum rows to get at a time from server. Range: 1 - 100.
					Might not be supported by some database systems.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="timeout" required="false" type="Numeric">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Maximum number of seconds that each action of a query is
					permitted to execute before returning an error. The
					cumulative time may exceed this value.

					For JDBC statements, CFML sets this attribute. For
					other drivers, check driver documentation.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="cachedafter" required="false" type="DateTime">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Date value (for example, April 16, 1999, 4-16-99). If date
					of original query is after this date, CFML uses
					cached query data. To use cached data, current query must
					use same SQL statement, data source, query name, user name,
					password.

					A date/time object is in the range 100 AD-9999 AD.

					When specifying a date value as a string, you must enclose
					it in quotation marks.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="cachedwithin" required="false" type="Timespan">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Timespan, using the CreateTimeSpan function. If original
					query date falls within the time span, cached query data is
					used. CreateTimeSpan defines a period from the present,
					back. Takes effect only if query caching is enabled in the
					Administrator.

					To use cached data, the current query must use the same SQL
					statement, data source, query name, user name, and password.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="debug" required="false" type="boolean">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Yes: If debugging is enabled, but the Administrator
						Database Activity option is not enabled, displays SQL
						submitted to datasource and number of records returned
						by query.
					No: If the Administrator Database Activity option is
						enabled, suppresses display.
				]]></help>
				<values>
					<value option="true" xml:base="http://localhost:8501/converter/inc/value_boolean.xml"/>
<value option="false" xml:base="http://localhost:8501/converter/inc/value_boolean.xml"/>
				</values>
			</parameter>
		</tag>
