<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tag xmlns="http://www.cfeclipse.org/version1/dictionary" creator="3" name="cfhttpparam" single="true" xmlstyle="false">
			<help><![CDATA[
				Allowed inside cfhttp tag bodies only. Required for cfhttp POST
				operations. Optional for all others. Specifies parameters to
				build an HTTP request.
			]]></help>
			<parameter name="type" required="true" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Information type
					* Header: The parameter specifies an HTTP header.
						CFML does not URL encode the header.
					* CGI: Specifies an HTTP header. CFML URL encodes
						the header by default.
					* Body: Specifies the body of the HTTP request. CFML
						does not URL encode the body contents.
					* XML: Identifies the request as having a content-type of
						text/xml. Specifies that the value attribute contains
						the body of the HTTP request. Used to send XML to the
						destination URL. CFML does not URL encode the XML
						data.
					* File: Tells CFML to send the contents of the
						specified file. CFML does not URL encode the
						file contents
					* URL: Specifies a URL query string name-value pair to
						append to the cfhttp url attribute. CFML URL
						encodes the query string.
					* FormField: Specifies a form field to send. CFML
						URL encodes the Form field by default.
					* Cookie: Specifies a cookie to send as an HTTP header.
						CFML URL encodes the cookie.
				]]></help>
				<values>
					<value option="header"/>
					<value option="cgi"/>
					<value option="body"/>
					<value option="xml"/>
					<value option="file"/>
					<value option="url"/>
					<value option="formfield"/>
					<value option="cookie"/>
				</values>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="name" required="false" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Variable name for data that is passed. Ignored for Body
					and XML types. For File type, specifies the filename to
					send in the request.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="value" required="false" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Value of the data that is sent. Ignored for File type. The
					value must contain string data or data that CFML can
					convert to a string for all type attributes except Body.
					Body types can have string or binary values.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="file" required="false" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Applies to File type; ignored for all other types. The
					absolute path to the file that is sent in the request body.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="encoded" required="false" type="boolean">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Applies to FormField and CGI types; ignored for all other
					types. Specifies whether to URLEncode the form field or
					header.
				]]></help>
				<values>
					<value option="true" xml:base="http://localhost:8501/converter/inc/value_boolean.xml"/>
<value option="false" xml:base="http://localhost:8501/converter/inc/value_boolean.xml"/>
				</values>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="mimetype" required="false" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Applies to File type; invalid for all other types.
					Specifies the MIME media type of the file contents.
					The content type can include an identifier for the
					character encoding of the file; for example, text/html;
					charset=ISO-8859-1 indicates that the file is HTML text in
					the ISO Latin-1 character encoding.
				]]></help>
				<values>
					<value option="text/plain"/>
					<value option="text/html"/>
				</values>
			</parameter>
		</tag>
