<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<cms_user>
		<userid>
			<label>userid</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The userid field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The userid field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
		</userid>
		<username>
			<label>username</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>45</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The username field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The username field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The username field is too long.  This field must be no more than 45 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</username>
		<password>
			<label>password</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>45</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The password field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The password field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The password field is too long.  This field must be no more than 45 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</password>
		<DisplayName>
			<label>DisplayName</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>100</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The DisplayName field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The DisplayName field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The DisplayName field is too long.  This field must be no more than 100 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</DisplayName>
		<bActive>
			<label>bActive</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The bActive field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The bActive field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
		</bActive>
		<bAdmin>
			<label>bAdmin</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The bAdmin field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The bAdmin field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
		</bAdmin>
		<dtLastLogin>
			<label>dtLastLogin</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The dtLastLogin field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a date value.</invalidType>
		</dtLastLogin>
		<email>
			<label>email</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>255</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The email field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The email field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The email field is too long.  This field must be no more than 255 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</email>
	</cms_user>
