<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<cms_article>
		<art_id>
			<label>art_id</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The art_id field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The art_id field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
		</art_id>
		<art_title>
			<label>art_title</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>255</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The art_title field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The art_title field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The art_title field is too long.  This field must be no more than 255 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</art_title>
		<art_description>
			<label>art_description</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>65535</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The art_description field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The art_description field is too long.  This field must be no more than 65535 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</art_description>
		<art_content>
			<label>art_content</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>65535</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The art_content field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The art_content field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The art_content field is too long.  This field must be no more than 65535 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</art_content>
		<dtcreated>
			<label>dtcreated</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The dtcreated field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a date value.</invalidType>
		</dtcreated>
		<dtDisplay>
			<label>dtDisplay</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The dtDisplay field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a date value.</invalidType>
		</dtDisplay>
		<userid>
			<label>userid</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The userid field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The userid field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
		</userid>
		<bPublished>
			<label>bPublished</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The bPublished field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The bPublished field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
		</bPublished>
		<art_type_id>
			<label>art_type_id</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The art_type_id field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<notProvided>The art_type_id field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
		</art_type_id>
		<art_img>
			<label>art_img</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>255</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The art_img field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The art_img field is too long.  This field must be no more than 255 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</art_img>
	</cms_article>
