<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<cms_testimonial>
		<tes_id>
			<label>tes_id</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The tes_id field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The tes_id field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
		</tes_id>
		<tes_teaser>
			<label>tes_teaser</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>65535</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The tes_teaser field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The tes_teaser field is too long.  This field must be no more than 65535 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</tes_teaser>
		<tes_text>
			<label>tes_text</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>65535</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The tes_text field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The tes_text field is too long.  This field must be no more than 65535 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</tes_text>
		<tes_person>
			<label>tes_person</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>85</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The tes_person field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The tes_person field is too long.  This field must be no more than 85 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</tes_person>
		<tes_jobtitle>
			<label>tes_jobtitle</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>85</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The tes_jobtitle field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The tes_jobtitle field is too long.  This field must be no more than 85 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</tes_jobtitle>
		<tes_company>
			<label>tes_company</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>85</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The tes_company field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The tes_company field is too long.  This field must be no more than 85 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</tes_company>
		<tes_url>
			<label>tes_url</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>166</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The tes_url field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The tes_url field is too long.  This field must be no more than 166 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</tes_url>
		<tes_image>
			<label>tes_image</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>85</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The tes_image field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The tes_image field is too long.  This field must be no more than 85 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</tes_image>
		<bPublished>
			<label>bPublished</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The bPublished field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The bPublished field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
		</bPublished>
	</cms_testimonial>
