<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tag xmlns="http://www.cfeclipse.org/version1/dictionary" creator="3" name="cfcookie" single="true" xmlstyle="false">
			<help><![CDATA[
				Defines web browser cookie variables, including expiration and
				security options.
			]]></help>
			<parameter name="name" required="true" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Name of cookie variable. CFML converts cookie names
					to all-uppercase. Cookie names set using this tag can
					include any printable ASCII characters except commas,
					semicolons or white space characters.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="value" required="false" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Value to assign to cookie variable. Must be a string or
					variable that can be stored as a string.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="expires" required="false" type="Object">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Expiration of cookie variable.

					* The default: the cookie expires when the user closes the
						browser, that is, the cookie is "session only".
					* A date or date/time object (for example, 10/09/97)
					* A number of days (for example, 10, or 100)
					* now: deletes cookie from client cookie.txt file
						(but does not delete the corresponding variable the
						Cookie scope of the active page).
					* never: The cookie expires in 30 years from the time it
						was created (effectively never in web years).
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="secure" required="false" type="boolean">
				<help><![CDATA[
					If browser does not support Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)
					security, the cookie is not sent. To use the cookie, the
					page must be accessed using the https protocol.
				]]></help>
				<values>
					<value option="true" xml:base="http://localhost:8501/converter/inc/value_boolean.xml"/>
<value option="false" xml:base="http://localhost:8501/converter/inc/value_boolean.xml"/>
				</values>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="path" required="false" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					URL, within a domain, to which the cookie applies;
					typically a directory. Only pages in this path can use the
					cookie. By default, all pages on the server that set the
					cookie can access the cookie.

					path = "/services/login"
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="domain" required="false" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Domain in which cookie is valid and to which cookie content
					can be sent from the user's system. By default, the cookie
					is only available to the server that set it. Use this
					attribute to make the cookie available to other servers.

					Must start with a period. If the value is a subdomain, the
					valid domain is all domain names that end with this string.
					This attribute sets the available subdomains on the site
					upon which the cookie can be used.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
		</tag>
