<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tag xmlns="http://www.cfeclipse.org/version1/dictionary" creator="3" name="cftable" single="false" xmlstyle="false">
			<help><![CDATA[
				Builds a table in a CFML page. This tag renders data as
				preformatted text, or, with the HTMLTable attribute, in an
				HTML table. If you do not want to write HTML table tag code, or
				if your data can be presented as preformatted text, use this
				tag.

				Preformatted text (defined in HTML with the <pre> and </pre>
				tags) displays text in a fixed-width font. It displays white
				space and line breaks exactly as they are written within the
				pre tags. For more information, see an HTML reference guide.

				To define table column and row characteristics, use the cfcol
				tag within this tag.
			]]></help>
			<parameter name="query" required="true" type="String">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Name of cfquery from which to draw data.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="maxrows" required="false" type="Numeric">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Maximum number of rows to display in the table.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="colspacing" required="false" type="Numeric">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Number of spaces between columns
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="headerlines" required="false" type="Numeric">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Number of lines to use for table header (the default leaves
					one line between header and first row of table).
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="htmltable" required="false" type="Any">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Renders data in an HTML 3.0 table.

					If you use this attribute (regardless of its value),
					CFML renders data in an HTML table.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="border" required="false" type="Any">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Displays border around table.

					If you use this attribute (regardless of its value),
					CFML displays a border around the table.

					Use this only if you use the HTMLTable attribute.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="colheaders" required="false" type="Any">
				<help><![CDATA[
					Displays column heads. If you use this attribute, you must
					also use the cfcol tag header attribute to define them.

					If you use this attribute (regardless of its value),
					CFML displays column heads.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
			<parameter name="startrow" required="false" type="Numeric">
				<help><![CDATA[
					The query result row to put in the first table row.
				]]></help>
				<values/>
			</parameter>
		</tag>
