<!-- NODE -->
<parameter name="datapath" type="String" required="false">
	<help>A pointer to the LzDatapath attached to this node, if  there 
		is one.</help>
	<values/>
</parameter>
<parameter name="defaultplacement" type="String" required="false">
	<help>An attribute used in container classes. If  set to a non-null 
		value, this forces this node to run its determinePlacement 
		method for any node whose parent is this node. If the subnode 
		has its own  placement attribute, determinePlacement will be 
		called with that value,  otherwise it will be called with this 
		value. Note that a class's  defaultplacement attribute only 
		applies to children in subclasses or in  instances, not to the 
		children of the class itself. This means that if a  class and 
		its subclass both define a defaultplacement attribute, the  
		attribute will be set to one value before the subclass children 
		are created  and to a different one after they are created. See 
		the determinePlacement method.</help>
	<values/>
</parameter>
<parameter name="id" type="String" required="false">
	<help>A global identifer for this node. If given, a pointer  to this
		 node with the given value will be placed in the global 
		 namespace</help>
	<values/>
</parameter>
<parameter name="initstage" type="String" required="false">
	<help>The execution of a node's init method and sending of the oninit 
		event is under the control of its initstage attribute</help>
	<values>
		<value option="early" />
		<value option="normal" />
		<value option="late" />
		<value option="immediate" />
		<value option="defer" />
	</values>
</parameter>
<parameter name="name" type="String" required="false">
	<help>The name for this subview. If given, then this node's parent
		 and immediate parent will use store a pointer to this node as 
		 the  given name value</help>
	<values />
</parameter>
<parameter name="oninit" type="Function" required="false">
	<help>The oninit script is executed once, after the element's 
		children, if any, have been initialized.</help>
	<values />
</parameter>
<parameter name="placement" type="Function" required="false">
	<help>Instructions to this element's container about where it should 
		go within the its container's internal hierarchy. See the 
		LzNode.determinePlacement method. Defaults to the container 
		itself.</help>
	<values />
</parameter>