<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Use Task-Focused UI">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This cheat sheet shows you how to handle a task lifecycle and how to use task-focused ui.<br/>
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Open the Plug-in perspective" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         If you&apos;re not already in Plug-in Development perspective in the main menu select <b>Window</b> &gt; <b>Open Perspective</b> &gt; 	<b>Other...</b> &gt; <b>Plug-in Development</b>	or click on the &quot;Click to Perform&quot; link below.
      </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective(org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective.perspectiveId=org.eclipse.pde.ui.PDEPerspective)"/>
   </item>
   <item title="Open the Task List view" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         If the Task List view is not opened, select in the main menu  <b>Window</b> &gt; <b>Show View</b> &gt; <b>Other...</b> &gt; <b>cfeclipse</b> &gt; <b>Task List</b> or click on the &quot;Click to Perform&quot; link below.
      </description>
      <command serialization="org.eclipse.ui.views.showView(org.eclipse.ui.views.showView.viewId=org.eclipse.cfeclipse.tasks.ui.views.TaskListView)" confirm="true">
      </command>
   </item>
   <item title="Create a sample project" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Before we start this cheat sheet, we need a project to practice.
<br/><br/>
In the main toolbar, click on the <b>New</b> button. Select the <b>Plug-in Project</b>  from the list then click on the <b>Next</b> button. Enter <b>SampleProject</b> for the project&apos;s name then click on the <b>Next</b> button twice.
Select from the Templates part <b>Hello, World</b> then click on the <b>Finish</b> button.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Create and activate a task" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         In the Task List view, click on the right mouse button, then select <b>New &gt; Category</b>. Enter <b>Tutorials</b> for the category&apos;s name.
<br/><br/>
Then right click on the <b>Tutorials</b> category and select <b>New &gt; Task</b>. Enter <b>Learn task-focus</b>  for the task&apos;s title and change the priority to <b>High</b>. You can add some notes,  too.
<br/><br/>
Right click on the new task and select <b>Activate</b> to activate the task.
<br/><br/>
<b>Important:</b> If it&apos;s not activated, click on the <b>&quot;Focus on the Active Task&quot;</b> toogle button in the <b>Package Explorer</b> and in the <b>Outline</b> view too.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Open SampleAction file" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Press down the <b>Ctrl+Shift+T</b> buttons or click on the &quot;Click to Perform&quot; link below. <br/> 
In the <b>Open Type</b> dialog  enter <b>SampleAction</b> for the type&apos;s name then press the <b>Enter</b> button.<br/> 
After the file is opened you can see the SampleAction class both  in the <b>Package Explorer</b> and in the <b>Outline</b> view.
      </description>
      <command serialization="org.eclipse.jdt.ui.navigate.open.type" confirm="true">
      </command>
   </item>
   <item title="Add method to focus" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Select in the Editor the <b>void run(IAction action)</b> method then you can see the <b>run(IAction)</b> method in the <b>Outline</b> view and in the <b>Package Explorer</b> under the SampleAction class.
<br/><br/>
Next press the Alt button and click on the SampleAction class in the <b>Outline</b> view.<br/> 
Now you can see all methods. Methods which aren&apos;t in the focus are in <b>grey</b> color. Select <b>window</b> field from the list. After that all methods will disappear which aren&apos;t in the focus.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Landmark" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         If an element&apos;s interest ranks high enough, it becomes a landmark, which is an implicitly created bookmark. Landmarks are showed in bold font.
<br/><br/>
Select the <b>run(IAction)</b> method in the <b>Outline</b> view or in the <b>Package Explorer</b>. Right click on the method and select <b>Mark as Landmark</b>. After then  this method becomes a landmark.
<br/><br/>
Also you can use key bindings. <b>Ctrl+Shift+Alt+UpArrow</b> to mark the element as landmark or <b>Ctrl+Shift+Alt+DownArrow</b> to mark less interesting for the element.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Remove method from focus" dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
         Right click on the <b>window</b> field and select <b>Remove from Focus</b>. The window field will disappear on the list.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Open Activator.java" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Press down the <b>Alt</b> button and <b>click</b> on the <b>src</b> directory. Then you can see 3 packages. <br/>
<b>Alt+click</b> on the  <b>sampleproject</b> package and you can open the Activator.java file with a simple double-click on the file name.
<br/><br/>
You can use <b>Alt+RightArrow</b> instead of <b>Alt+click</b>.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Quick Context View" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         Press down <b>Ctrl+Shift+Alt+RightArrow</b> buttons, then you can see all elements which are in the focus.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Complete task" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         In the Task List view, click on the right mouse button on the <b>Learn task-focus</b> task and select deactivate.
<br/>
Click again on the task with the right mouse button and select <b>Mark &gt; Complete</b>. <br/>
After then the task&apos;s name will be struck through.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
